

+91 9996632053



Noida, India

Meticulous Software Engineer with 3+ years of experience designing and developing software solutions. In-depth understanding of web technologies with focus on delivering innovative business solutions. Excels in fast-paced, high-energy and deadline-driven environment with willingness to take on additional tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager Bada Business Pvt. Ltd.

11/2022 - Present Software Engineer (ReactJs) New Delhi, India

Software Engineer Chetu India Pvt. Ltd.

06/2021 - 09/2022 Software Engineer (ReactJs Developer) Noida, India

Achievements/Tasks

- Developed 4+ web applications, Components using variety of engineering languages and Improved and designed new layouts to achieve usability.
- Worked with backend developers to implement prototype elements into web applications.
- Attended scrum meetings and attended the client call weekly and present the live demonstration to stakeholder.

Web Developer

Visiweb Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

12/2019 - 06/2021

Noida, india

Fullstack Web Developer Achievements/Tasks

- Designed websites, portals and large-scale web applications for multiple clients
- Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML and CSS3, Bootstrap 4, ReactJs, PHP
- Developed web-based PHP and ReactJS applications for deployment on premiums service platforms.

FullStack Web Developer

SachTech Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

06/2019 - 11/2019

Mohali, india

- Achievements/Tasks
- learn about backend languages (PHP, CI) and Built website content and designs using HTML and CSS.
- Collaborated with web developer to accept assignments and support administrative tasks for design and development.
- Set up SQL queries and other database management responsibilities.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Science and Engineering

CDL Government Polytechnic College

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Appreciated by college and won the trophy many times in dance competition.

Appreciated by Chetu India Pvt Ltd for best dance performance in competition.

Certification in PHP by SachTech Solutions Pvt Ltd.

Certification in soft Skills by Mahindra Pride Classrooms.

Certification in soft Skills SachTech Solutions Pvt Ltd.

PROJECTS

Novuskin Med Spa

- Worked as frontend developer and developed a dashboard and some configuration components.
- Impelemt the Graph chart and export thier data.
- Represnt the campains data on dashboard in chart format.
- Implement RESTful API and JWT token for authentication.

Apprent

- Implement third party property management RESTfull API.
- Implement webhooks for get data from third party application.
- Implement API for create workorders in property management.

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Dance Travelling

Hiking

Badminton

07/2016 - 05/2019

Sirsa, Haryana